http://www.intra-focus.com/focus/DOCS/privacy.htm

Our Internet Privacy Policy
Our Internet Marketing Privacy Policy
OUR PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FOR UPDATES & CHANGES.
This website is not directed at persons under the age of 18 (eighteen). By registering on this website through the submission of the information or call-back request, you agree that the following terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy shall govern our use and disclosure of your personal information. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, please do not complete the information request form (i.e., do not register or use the call-back feature) or otherwise use or access this website. If you have already registered by completing the information disclosure forms, and you wish to opt-out from receiving more information, click the "unsubscribe" link on the bottom right of all e-mail campaigns.
Your e-mail address will be added to the suppression files associated with this Website within ten (10) business days of your request. Thereafter, you should not receive any email or phone correspondence from us.
This Privacy Policy describes in some detail the information that we collect from you as part of the normal operation of our service, and what may happen to the information we collect.
Your privacy is very important to us
We understand that some of the information that you might provide on our Website is personal and private. By submitting your personal information, you are entrusting us to handle information that you regard as private, for the purposes and in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy. In exchange for your trust, you expect us to handle your personal and private information in a professional manner that will be in keeping with your trust. Our Privacy Policy explains what information we obtain on this Website, and how we use the information disclosed to us to link you to our clients who have expressed a willingness to provide you with the products and services associated with this Website.
Who We Are
We are an advertising & marketing agency in Georgetown, Texas that handles Internet marketing for our clients.
IF Marketing
& Advertising | 807 Rock St., Suite 103 | Georgetown, TX 78626
Information We Collect
The information that we collect is generally limited to personal information about you that our clients consider necessary for performing a preliminary evaluation of your qualifications. To the extent that you can order products, enter contests, express an opinion, or subscribe to a service(s), the type of personally identifiable information that may be collected may include: name; address; e-mail address; telephone number; fax number; credit card information; information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services; education level; educational interests; home owner status; income; debt level; current mortgage; mortgage rate and the like. To the extent that you are requested and you do submit information about other people, such information will be limited recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.
We also collect user information that can help us optimize and enhance your experience on our Website; as well as provide you with an efficient, safe, smooth, and customized experience. For example, if you came to this Website from an online banner ad, pop-up or other advertisement, an anonymous identification number may be passed to our Website. In some cases, we may place a cookie in your browser. The aforementioned information cannot, by itself, be used to gather any personally identifiable information about you, but it will allow us to track the overall effectiveness of our online advertising campaigns. We also automatically track certain information with respect to your behavior on the Website through the forgoing cookie or identification number. This non personally identifiable information may include the Internet address or URL that you just came from and which URL you go to next; your computer browser information; and your IP address. We use this non personally identifiable information in conjunction with some of the information that you provided to us to do internal research on our users' demographics and behavior; and to better understand how to best serve other users of this Website. Third parties may also set cookies on our websites to determine proper website usage and click count.
We also utilize Web Logs to track aggregate information about how our website is being used. Web Logs track anonymous user information, including but not limited to the number of visitors to our website, operating systems and browser type. Unlike cookies, Web Logs are maintained only on our servers and do not store or place anything on the user's computer.
How We Use Your Information
We collect the information that you submit and which our clients consider necessary for performing a preliminary evaluation of your qualifications for their products and services. Prior to sending your information to our clients, we attempt to validate it. For example, we may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions, and accuracy based upon past usage and response; or compare your information against other publicly available files; or validate some of the personal information submitted to verify that the information inputted has a high probability of being valid information.
After we submit your information to our clients, our clients may begin a separate and independent evaluation of the information you submitted
WE MAY USE INFORMATION THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE
For example, we may share your personal information with select clients so that they can contact you and offer you products and or services that we believe might be of interest to you. This may include e-mail advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, and online banner advertising to name a few. In addition, we may maintain separate e-mail, mailing or phone lists for different purposes based on the information that you submitted and that we maintain. For your information, our clients have all agreed to operate in accordance with federal and state laws and regulations relating to the handling of your personal information. You may learn more about any of our client's privacy policy by visiting our clients' websites at such times as such client may contact you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of our clients' websites. If you wish to end any e-mail correspondence from us, you will need to Opt-out from receiving further correspondence by advising us of your decision to Opt-out by clicking a link in the e-mail to our Opt-out procedures. Within ten (10) business days, your e-mail address will be placed on a suppression list and we will no longer correspond with you by email or resell or transfer your information to third parties. If you wish to end future correspondence with any of our clients, you will need to follow the instructions at the end of any such each e-mail message from them to unsubscribe from such client's e-mail. You are able to opt-out when registering with us.
We may also disclose your personally identifiable information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process; as well as the transfer or sale of personally identifiable information pursuant to the sale of our business or assets. Should such a combination or acquisition occur, we will require that the new combined or acquiring entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If we transfer ownership of the website to another company, we will notify you by email or by general notice on our website. In addition to the forgoing, we may also sell, transfer or share non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons visiting this website.
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept personal data or access our servers and obtain personal data. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, nor you should not expect, that your personal information would always remain private.
Certain sensitive information such as credit card numbers or other information such as social security numbers and drivers licenses ("Financial Information") collected on the website and associated data is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software from the time it is captured by our application to the time it is transmitted to our servers. For more information on the encryption and protection of your information, please see How We Protect Your Privacy.
Application of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on the IF Marketing & Advertising website. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing
How We Protect Your Privacy
We protect your privacy in a number of ways. As an initial matter, any Financial Information transmitted to our servers via a secure server is encrypted using SSL technology. SSL is a protocol that transmits your communications over the Internet in an encrypted form. The protocol ensures that the information is sent, unchanged, only to the server you intended to send it to.
Once your information reaches our server, it is protected by a firewall. With a firewall in place, your information is virtually inaccessible to third parties. In addition to encryption and firewall protections, we have all of our clients agree to operate in accordance with federal and state laws and regulations, including regulations relating to CAN-SPAM and rules promulgated by the FTC. If we learn that any of our clients are breaching our agreement, and therefore your trust, we will take corrective actions immediately or terminate our relationship with such client.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on our website, you can mail us at the address indicated below in the Contact Us section.
Changes and Opting-Out
If you want to change the information that you submitted, please do so by making another request through our Website. We will not be able to change information that is forwarded on to our clients. Please contact the clients directly to change any of your information.
If you want to request to be removed from further communication with this Website, including our Premium Services, please Opt-out by clicking this link to our Opt-out procedure. We will place your e-mail address on a suppression file associated with this Website. Persons whose names appear on our suppression file, will have their e-mail addresses checked against all correspondence to be sent by us. Where there is a match, the planned email correspondence will be withheld, and such person will receive no further email correspondence from us. Your e-mail address will be placed on the suppression list associated with this Website within ten business (10) days of your request. Once you have opted out, we will no longer forward you email from this website but we are not responsible or in control of the business practices of our clients who have been forwarded your information.
Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy on the Website. Be sure to check the current terms of any privacy policy in effect by visiting this Website. By checking the effective date of the policy, you will be immediately alerted on whether the Privacy Policy has been updated. Please note however, that the updated privacy policy will go into effect automatically 30 (thirty) days after initial posting.
From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. Please note that if our information practices change at some time in the future, we will use only data collected from the time of the new privacy policy amendment forward for those new purposes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: ATTN: Privacy Policy |
IF Marketing & Advertising | 807 Rock St., Suite 103 | Georgetown, TX 78626
Special Notification for California Residents
Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following mailing address: CA Privacy Request, ATTN: IF Marketing & Advertising | 807 Rock St., Suite 103 | Georgetown, TX 78626. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.
